How to claim cashless two-wheeler insurance The
procedure varies depending on the type of claim
[Music]
In case of theft claimant,
follow these steps: File an FIR immediately and
inform your insurer Submit your two-wheeler documents If the
vehicle cannot be traced within a certain period, the police will be able to trace it. A
non-traceable
certificate will be
issued. On this basis, the insurer will settle the claim in the total loss
category and pay up to the IDV In
case of third-party claimant, follow these steps:
Inform the police and the insurer immediately After registering your claim, the insurance company will
send it to the Insurance Claims Tribunal as an award. After
verification, the Insurance
Claims Tribunal will decide the amount to be paid In
case of self-damage claimant,
follow these steps: Inform the
insurer about the damages
An
investigation officer will be
appointed to inspect the damages After the survey, the
officer will send
a permit to the network garage to start the repair work
You will be provided with services from the network garage  If
received, the insurer will settle the repair costs
directly with the garage.
In the case of a non-network garage, the amount will be paid as per the terms and conditions of the policy.
Visit www.colasibazar where you can compare and choose from various
categories of two-wheeler insurance
policies.
So, before buying two-wheeler insurance,
visit Police Bazaar
[Music]